<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:ns1="urn:oasis:names:tc:xliff:document:1.2">
    <color name="common_action_bar_splitter">#d2d2d2</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_dark_text_default">@android:color/white</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_dark_text_disabled">#FFAAAAAA</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_dark_text_focused">@android:color/white</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_dark_text_pressed">@android:color/white</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_default_background">#FFDD4B39</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_light_text_default">#FF737373</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_light_text_disabled">#FFAAAAAA</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_light_text_focused">#FF737373</color>
    <color name="common_signin_btn_light_text_pressed">@android:color/white</color>
    <declare-styleable name="MapAttrs"><attr format="enum" name="mapType">
      <enum name="none" value="0"/>
      <enum name="normal" value="1"/>
      <enum name="satellite" value="2"/>
      <enum name="terrain" value="3"/>
      <enum name="hybrid" value="4"/>
    </attr><attr format="float" name="cameraBearing"/><attr format="float" name="cameraTargetLat"/><attr format="float" name="cameraTargetLng"/><attr format="float" name="cameraTilt"/><attr format="float" name="cameraZoom"/><attr format="boolean" name="uiCompass"/><attr format="boolean" name="uiRotateGestures"/><attr format="boolean" name="uiScrollGestures"/><attr format="boolean" name="uiTiltGestures"/><attr format="boolean" name="uiZoomControls"/><attr format="boolean" name="uiZoomGestures"/><attr format="boolean" name="useViewLifecycle"/><attr format="boolean" name="zOrderOnTop"/></declare-styleable>
    <dimen name="activity_horizontal_margin">16dp</dimen>
    <dimen name="activity_vertical_margin">16dp</dimen>
    <string name="app_name">Harbinger</string>
    <string name="auth_client_availability_notification_title">Install/Update/Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string name="auth_client_play_services_err_notification_msg">Google Play services error</string>
    <string name="auth_client_requested_by_msg">Requested by <ns1:g id="app_name">%1$s</ns1:g></string>
    <string msgid="2523291102206661146" name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string msgid="227660514972886228" name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">This app won\'t work unless you enable Google Play services.</string>
    <string msgid="5122002158466380389" name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string msgid="7153882981874058840" name="common_google_play_services_install_button">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string msgid="2122112764540849864" name="common_google_play_services_install_text_phone">This app won\'t run without Google Play services, which are missing from your phone.</string>
    <string msgid="7351599665250191022" name="common_google_play_services_install_text_tablet">This app won\'t run without Google Play services, which are missing from your tablet.</string>
    <string msgid="7215213145546190223" name="common_google_play_services_install_title">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">Unknown issue with Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">Google Play services, which some of your applications rely on, is not supported by your device. Please contact the manufacturer for assistance.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_title">Google Play services</string>
    <string msgid="6556509956452265614" name="common_google_play_services_update_button">Update</string>
    <string msgid="9053896323427875356" name="common_google_play_services_update_text">This app won\'t run unless you update Google Play services.</string>
    <string msgid="1788179980625863495" name="common_google_play_services_update_title">Update Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">Sign in</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text_long">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="dos_and_donts">BEFORE Stay away from those areas that may have been the target of terrorism in the past. Be aware of the conduct of people around you. Look out for objects that should not be there, that cannot be accounted for or that are out of place. Under no circumstances should any suspicious package be touched, moved or otherwise disturbed. If at any time a package or other object is observed in an area where it should not be or under circumstances that give cause for suspicion, the Security Officer should be notified. The area around suspicious packages should be evacuated to at least 300 feet in all directions. There must be no mobile radio or cellular phone transmission within 300 feet of a suspicious package or object. Draw a plan or map of the building area where the suspicious package or object is found to be given to police to assist them in locating the package. Stay away from large gatherings or demonstrations. Be observant and alert. If something doesn’t look or feel right, it probably isn’t. When using public transport: Check below the seat for any unattended bag / packet. Be alert of someone leaving the train / bus without taking his belongings. If you hear about any incident: Confirm its factual accuracy and ensure it’s not a rumour. Please avoid spreading any rumours as they can actually lead to an incident (e.g. stampede etc). DURING DO’S Stay calm. Do not panic. Remember that staircases and basements provide immediate protection from the blast, its effects and falling glass. Avoid calling any one. Please send SMS only. Huge amount of load is put on communication infrastructure during an emergency. Avoid crowds. Crowds may be targeted for a second attack. Avoid unattended cars, trucks or other vehicles. They may contain explosives. Stay far away from damaged buildings to avoid falling glass and bricks. Hear television and radio reports to keep you updated of the situation. In case of an explosion take cover under a sturdy table or desk if things are falling around you. When the situation is better, leave quickly, watching for weakened floors, stairways and falling debris. Move away from exit routes to be used by emergency officials. If fire alarm has not been activated, remember that fire doors will NOT be free swinging. Break the emergency door release to enable fast egress. You will know where you are in the building with the signs for the floors. DON’TS Do not run, you may be suspected as the bomber. If you are in a crowd, stay at the fringes. Do not return to the impacted area. Do not try to manage the situation alone. Don’t stand in front of windows, glass doors or other hazardous areas. AFTER Don’t travel unless absolutely essential. Return to the affected area only after approval from Emergency Response Personnel. Seek counselling if you have been affected by the incident.</string>
    <string name="location_client_ulr_inactive_age_under_13" translatable="false">
        AgeUnder13
    </string>
    <string name="location_client_ulr_inactive_age_unknown" translatable="false">AgeUnknown</string>
    <string name="location_client_ulr_inactive_unknown_restriction" translatable="false">
        UnknownRestriction
    </string>
    <string formatted="false" name="proactive_preparation">Stay vigilant. Remember that violence can happen anytime, anywhere. At your local mall, open marketplace, train station, school functions, or your office building. Look for things and people that are out of place For example, a suit case or brief case sitting in the middle of the food court at a shopping mall should set off alarm bells. While we are not ones to judge a person’s character by the color of their skin or ethnicity, the fact is, that modern day extremism targeting the West, in the majority of cases, originates from Arab-born individuals. It is human nature to make initial judgments based on external features, so “profiling” is something that you probably already engage in on a regular basis. If you have flown in the last eight years, and you noticed a group of what seemed to be a Muslim men, chances are you already prejudged what they may or may not be. Don’t feel bad about profiling, because the fact is, all humans do it. Profiling, combined with other observations, such as looking for typical features of someone under stress like sweating, shifting eyes, and anxious behaviors could act as a potential indicator for a developing threat. Look for exits. While there is no need to panic when going into public places, as the probabilities are still low that you would be in a target area, identifying emergency exists routes as you enter an area is one of the first things to consider. Look for secondary and emergency exits. In an emergency, chances are that the majority of those in your immediate vicinity will default to their entry point as an exist. This means that a good 90% of people will be rushing the same exit. When seconds count, and a mass of people starts to panic, you would be better served taking an alternative exit. Prepare an evacuation route. Similar to the point above, in the event of a city-wide or regional terrorist attack or other emergency, most people will evacuate via major highway arteries. Knowing these arteries and then avoiding them may save you precious minutes or hours as you evacuate an area that may have been hit by a chemical, biological or nuclear (tactical, suitcase, dirty) weapon. Plan your evacuation routes now. It only takes a few minutes via online mapping technology. Either print your evacuation maps, or obtain traditional maps of your local area, region and state. Prepare a Bug Out Bag Pack a 72 hour bag(s) that includes, but is not limited to, supplies like emergency food (MRE, Freeze Dried Pouches, Emergency Dietary Bars), Water filter/Purification Tablets, money, basic medical supplies, clothing, multi-tool, backup maps, address book/contact lists, tent and sleeping bags. A 72 hour emergency evacuation pack is the bare minimum. Be sure to consider all family members and dietary requirements when packing your bag(s). A 5000 cubic inch bag, generally used for trekking, could provide a 10 – 14 day buffer for a single individual if it is packed correctly. Water Have at least 10 gallons of water (two of those large 5 gallon jugs) on hand at all times. In the event of an emergency, your water supply may be inoperable or contaminated, so having some on hand to throw into your bug-out vehicle could be a life saver. Self Defense When millions of people hit the streets in an evacuation, there will undoubtadly be those who were not prepared and will take whatever measures they deem necessary to acquire food, water and a ride out of town. Be prepared to take defensive measures in the event you and your family come under threat. Remember, though, that your main goal is to evacuate, not to be involved in altercations, so use force to defend yourself only as a last resort. When your gas tank is half-full, it’s empty To ensure you never run out of gas, make it a habit to fill up anytime your gas gauge gets below 50%. Most vehicles will be able to get you at least 125 miles of continuous driving on a half tank of gas. If possible, having a reserve gas container (5 – 10 gallons) would also be a good idea. Know where you’re going If you have to evacuate, you should establish multiple bug-out locations outside your general area of residence. Contact family and friends and work out emergency shelter in the event of a catastrophe. If you do not have friends or family outside of your city, then consider adding hotels, motels or camp grounds, with phone numbers, addresses and directions to your evacuation planning. Go with your gut The fight or flight response of humans has been honed over the last 200,000 years. Some call it intuition. Let it work in your favor. In emergencies, you will have a heightened sense of awareness, and coupled with your preparedness planning, your intuition may play an important roll. Listen and act accordingly. Plan on Plan A not working Also plan on Plan B not working. It is impossible to predict when and how disaster will strike. Having a plan not only gets you prepared and provides you with a check list to execute in the event of an emergency, but also prepares your mind for the unexpected. While you may not know exactly what you’re not expecting, the fact that you know there are unknowns going into it makes you that much more prepared. Surviving an emergency, in many instances, will not come down to how good of a plan you put together. It will come down to how prepared your mind is to handle dynamic, fluid situations under stress. Stay optimistic and believe in your ability to continue moving forward no matter what difficulties come your way.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="safety_guidelines">Because most bombings occur in public places, your family should know what to do in the event of an explosion. As with any emergency drill, parents should practice the following tips with age appropriate children and discuss what to do in the event of being trapped in or being near the scene of a bombing. Remember, the goal is to empower your children with knowledge, not to frighten them. If your family is trapped in debris, you should: use a flashlight to signal your location to rescuers, if possible. avoid unnecessary movement so you don’t stir the dust. cover your nose and mouth with some sort of material that is nearby, to breathe through. Dense-weave cotton material acts as a good filter, or you may wet the material before breathing through it to help filter the dust. tap on a pipe or wall so rescuers can hear where you are. use a whistle to signal rescuers, if possible. shout as a last resort, only. Shouting can cause you to inhale dangerous amount of dust. If your family is near the scene of an explosion, you should: get under a sturdy table or desk if things are falling around you. When the items stop falling, leave quickly. Watch for obviously weakened floors and stairways, and be especially vigilant about falling debris. Do not use elevators. follow your family, job, or school emergency disaster plan for leaving and staying away from the explosion. Do not stop to retrieve personal possessions or make any calls or texts. Do not return to the scene because you will increase the risk of danger for rescue workers and your family. avoid crowds. Crowds of people may be the target of a second attack. avoid unattended cars and trucks, as these may contain explosives. do not stand in front of windows, glass doors, or other potentially dangerous areas, including damaged buildings. Move at least 10 blocks or 200 yards away from damaged buildings. Also remember to move away from sidewalks or streets that will be used by emergency officials or other people still exiting the building. follow directions from people in authority, including police, fire, EMS, military personnel, school supervisors, or workplace supervisors. call 911 once you are in a safe place, but only if police, fire, or EMS has not arrived to help injured people. help others who are hurt or need assistance to leave the area if you are able to do so. If you see someone who is seriously injured, seek help. Do not attempt to manage the situation alone. listen to your radio or television for news and instructions.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="survuival_guidelines">Remain calm and be patient.Follow the advice of local emergency officials.Listen to your radio or television for news and instructions.If the event occurs near you, check for injuries. Give first aid and get help for seriously injured people.If the event occurs near your home while you are there, check for damage using a flashlight. Do not light matches or candles or turn on electrical switches. Check for fires, fire hazards and other household hazards. Sniff for gas leaks, starting at the water heater. If you smell gas or suspect a leak, turn off the main gas valve, open windows, and get everyone outside quickly.Shut off any other damaged utilities.Confine or secure your pets.Call your family contact—do not use the telephone again unless it is a life-threatening emergency.Check on your neighbors, especially those who are elderly or disabled.</string>
    <string formatted="false" name="what_is_terrorism">\u2022 Terrorism is not new and even though it has been used since the early times of recorded history, it can be relatively hard to define terrorism. Terrorism has been described variously as both a tactic and strategy; a crime and a holy duty       ; a justified reaction to oppression and an inexcusable abomination. Obviously, a lot depends on whose point of view is being represented. Terrorism has often been an effective tactic for the weaker side in a conflict. As an asymmetric form of conflict, it confers coercive power with many of the advantages of military force at a fraction of the cost. Due to the secretive nature and small size of terrorist organizations, they often offer opponents no clear organization to defend against or to deter. That is why pre-emption is being considered to be so important. In some cases, terrorism has been a means to carry on a conflict without the adversary realizing the nature of the threat, mistaking terrorism for criminal activity. Because of these characteristics, terrorism has become increasingly common among those pursuing extreme goals throughout the world. But despite its popularity, terrorism can be a nebulous concept. Even within the U.S. Government, agencies responsible for different functions in the ongoing fight against terrorism and extremism use different definitions. The United States Department of Defense defines terrorism as “the calculated use of unlawful violence or threat of unlawful violence to inculcate fear; intended to coerce or to intimidate governments or societies in the pursuit of goals that are generally political, religious, or ideological.” Within this definition, there are three key elements—violence, fear, and intimidation—and each element produces terror in its victims. The FBI uses this definition: \'Terrorism is the unlawful use of force and violence against persons or property to intimidate or coerce a government, the civilian population, or any segment thereof, in furtherance of political or social objectives.\' The U.S. Department of State defines terrorism to be \'premeditated politically-motivated violence perpetrated against non-combatant targets by sub-national groups or clandestine agents, usually intended to influence an audience\'. Outside the United States Government, there are greater variations in what features of terrorism are emphasized in definitions. The United Nations produced the following definition of terrorism in 1992; \'An anxiety-inspiring method of repeated violent action, employed by (semi-) clandestine individual, group or state actors, for idiosyncratic, criminal or political reasons, whereby - in contrast to assassination - the direct targets of violence are not the main targets.\' The most commonly accepted academic definition starts with the U.N. definition quoted above, and adds two sentences totalling another 77 words on the end; containing such verbose concepts as \'message generators\' and \'violence based communication processes\'. Less specific and considerably less verbose, the British Government definition of terrorism from 1974 is \'…the use of violence for political ends, and includes any use of violence for the purpose of putting the public, or any section of the public, in fear.\'</string>
    <style name="AppBaseTheme" parent="android:Theme.NoTitleBar.Fullscreen">
        <!--
            Theme customizations available in newer API levels can go in
            res/values-vXX/styles.xml, while customizations related to
            backward-compatibility can go here.
        -->
    </style>
    <style name="AppTheme" parent="AppBaseTheme">
        <!-- All customizations that are NOT specific to a particular API-level can go here. -->
    </style>
</resources>